Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Environmental Action, 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 1 - 41 Folders: 1 - 1126
  - Subseries 1.13: Southside, 1.13; Boxes: 19 - 20 Folders: 564 - 641
    - Petitioners’ Memo in support of the Petition (Folder 628, Box 20)
    - Planning Board Meetings (Folder 629, Box 20)
    - Press (Folder 630, Box 20)
    - Record Exhibits (Folder 631, Box 20)
    - Responses to Decision on Petition (Folder 632, Box 20)
    - Rezoning (Folder 633, Box 20)
    - RM Toole Correspondence 1985 (Folder 634, Box 20)
    - Stipulation of Settlement (Folder 635, Box 20)
    - Stover Affidavit (Folder 636, Box 20)
    - Useful Papers (Research) (Folder 637, Box 20)
    - Verified Answer (Folder 638, Box 20)
    - Verified Answer of Respondent Springside Assoc. (Folder 639, Box 20)
    - Verified Reply (Folder 640, Box 20)
    - Where the Public Met Nature and Art (Folder 641, Box 20)
  - Subseries 1.14: Route 9A Reconstruction, 1.14; Box: 21 Folders: 642 - 658
    Series contains plans for the reconstruction of Route 9A.
    - Route 9A Reconstruction (Folder 642, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Chapters 1-6 (Folder 643, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Chapters 7-20 (Folder 644, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Chapters 21-Index (Folder 645, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix A: Technical Engineering Drawings (See Also: Oversized Box) (Folder 646, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix B: Land Use and Socioeconomic Conditions (Folder 647, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix C: Cultural Resources (Folder 648, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix D: Visual Resources (Folder 649, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix E: Traffic and Public Transportation, Vol. 1 (Folder 650, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix E: Traffic and Public Transportation, Vol. 2 (Folder 651, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix F: Pedestrians and Bicyclists (Folder 652, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix G: Air Quality (Folder 653, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix H: Noise (Folder 654, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix I: Coastal Zone Management (Folder 655, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix J: Contaminated Materials (Folder 656, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix K: Agency and Public Participation and Coordination (Folder 657, Box 21)
    - Route 9A Reconstruction Project Final Environmental Impact Statement: Appendix L: Agency and Public Comments on the DEIS/SDEIS (Folder 658, Box 21)
  - Subseries 1.15: Andre Mele Files, 1.15; Box: 22 Folders: 659 - 795
    Series contains documents and publications used by Andre Mele for research and writing
    - Articles (Folder 659, Box 22)
    - Brochures (Folder 660, Box 22)
    - Clean and Calm Waters Group (Folder 661, Box 22)
    - Contaminants in Hudson River Striped Bass, 1978-1985 (Folder 662, Box 22)
    - DEC Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife: May 1-Nov.1, 1981 (Folder 663, Box 22)
    - DEC Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife: Nov. 1, 1981-April 30, 1982 (Folder 664, Box 22)
    - Edison Excerpts (Folder 665, Box 22)
    - Final New York State Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Plan (Draft) and General Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 666, Box 22)
    - Fish for the Future: A Citizen’s Guide to Federal Marine Fisheries Management (Folder 667, Box 22)
    - Hazardous Wastes: The Legislative Record - A Compendium of Hazardous Waste Legislation (Folder 668, Box 22)
    - Hercules Engines (Folder 669, Box 22)
    - Hudson River Angler Survey, March 1993 (Folder 670, Box 22)
    - IBOX Seminar Also OCON Term Paper (Folder 671, Box 22)
    - Inter/Port (Folder 672, Box 22)
    - Key Calculations (PFP) (Folder 673, Box 22)
    - The Lake Book: A Guide to Reducing Water Pollution at Home (Folder 674, Box 22)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Library (Folder 675, Box 22)
    - Managing Dredged Material (Folder 676, Box 22)
    - Map of Train Stations (Folder 677, Box 22)
    - Motorboat Contamination, Jet Skis (Folder 678, Box 22)
    - Motorless Otsego (Folder 679, Box 22)
    - New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remedial Plan, July 1, 1993 (Folder 680, Box 22)
    - PCB in Striped Bass from the Marine District of New York, 1985 (Folder 681, Box 22)
    - Personal Watercraft Misc. Notes (Folder 682, Box 22)
    - Photographs (Folder 683, Box 22)
    - Polluting the Hudson: A Gentlemen’s Agreement (Folder 684, Box 22)
    - Polluting the Hudson: Business as Usual (Folder 685, Box 22)
    - Public Participation (Folder 686, Box 22)
    - Research Groups/Organizations (Folder 687, Box 22)
    - Remedial Action Report FY 1992-1993 (Folder 688, Box 22)
    - Scott D. MacEwan (Folder 689, Box 22)
    - A Spatial and Seasonal Study of the Benthic Fauna of the Lower Bay of New York Harbor, Draft May 1988 (Folder 690, Box 22)
    - Synopsis: “Polluting for Pleasure” (Folder 691, Box 22)
    - Temporal and Spatial Aspects of PCB Contamination in Hudson River Striped Bass (Folder 692, Box 22)
    - Thesis - Sea Surface Films (Folder 693, Box 22)
    - Studies - Motorboat Contamination (Folder 694, Box 22)
    - Voices From the River: Keys to Successful Community Based River Conservation (Folder 695, Box 22)
  - Subseries 1.16: Toxic Waste, 1.16; Boxes: 23 - 25 Folders: 696 - 760
    Series contains documents and publications concerning the exposure and disposal of toxic waste
    - 1990 Toxics Release Inventory (Folder 696, Box 23)
    - 1991 Toxics Release Inventory (Folder 697, Box 23)
    - An Analysis of the Ineffectiveness of the New York State Toxic (Folder 698, Box 23)
    - An Ounce of Toxic Pollution Prevention (Folder 699, Box 23)
    - Biomonitoring to Achieve Control of Toxic Effluants (Folder 700, Box 23)
    - Clippings (Folder 701, Box 23)
    - Common Synonyms for Chemicals Listed Under the Emergency (Folder 702, Box 23)
    - Correspondence (Folder 703, Box 23)
    - County Toxic Waste Samples (Folder 704, Box 23)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation Toxic Waste Technical (Folder 705, Box 23)
    - Environmental Action Foundation Right to Know Fact Sheets (Folder 706, Box 23)
    - Environmental Dividends: Cutting More Chemical Wastes (Folder 707, Box 23)
    - Facility Pollution Prevention Planning (Folder 708, Box 23)
    - Fifth Annual Report on Carcinogens (Folder 709, Box 23)
    - Integrating Pollution Prevention with Total Quality Management (Folder 710, Box 23)
    - Manufacturing Pollution: A Survey of the Nation’s Toxic Polluters (Folder 711, Box 23)
    - Middlesex County: Hazardous to Your Health? (Folder 712, Box 23)
    - Municipal Wastewater (Folder 713, Box 23)
    - New York State Toxic Release Inventory Reviews (Folder 714, Box 23)
    - Phantom Reductions: Tracking Toxic Trends (Folder 715, Box 23)
    - Poisons in our Neighborhoods: Toxic Pollution in New Jersey (Folder 716, Box 23)
    - Policy Alternatives on Environment (Folder 717, Box 23)
    - Pollution Prevention: Environmental Protection Agency (Folder 718, Box 23)
    - Pollution Prevention EPA Fact Sheets (Folder 719, Box 24)
    - Pollution Prevention: General (Folder 720, Box 24)
    - Putting Prevention First (Folder 721, Box 24)
    - Radon: Risk, Reality and Reason (Folder 722, Box 24)
    - The Ravaged River: Toxic Chemicals in the Niagara River (Folder 723, Box 24)
    - The Recycling Loophole in the Toxics Release Inventory (Folder 724, Box 24)
    - Report of Joint Public Hearings on Toxic Chemical Accidents in New York State (Folder 725, Box 24)
    - Report of the Fixed Station Toxics Surveillance Network 1985 (Folder 726, Box 24)
    - Report on Chemical Emissions of the Members of the Alliance of Chemical Industries of New York State Inc. (Folder 727, Box 24)
    - The Right to Know Act (Folder 728, Box 24)
    - The Right to Know More (Folder 729, Box 24)
    - SPDES Regulatory Sampling (Folder 730, Box 24)
    - State Toxic Pollution Statistics (Folder 731, Box 24)
    - Toxic Chemical Accident Risks in New York City (Folder 732, Box 24)
    - Toxic Chemical Release Inventory Questions and Answers (Folder 733, Box 24)
    - Toxic Chemical Release Inventory Reporting Form R and Instructions (Folder 734, Box 24)
    - Toxic Release Data Facilities in Bennington, Vermont (Folder 735, Box 24)
    - Toxic Release: General Press (Folder 736, Box 24)
    - Toxic Release Health Effects (Folder 737, Box 24)
    - Toxic Release Inventory Miscellaneous (Folder 738, Box 24)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife 1979 and 1980 Annual Reports, Vol. 4, No. 1 (Folder 739, Box 24)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife Nov. 1, 1981-April 30, 1982, Vol. 5, No. 1 (Folder 740, Box 24)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife Analysis since May 1, 1982, Vol. 6 (Folder 741, Box 24)
    - Toxic Tides 1989 (Folder 742, Box 24)
    - Toxic Tides II (Folder 743, Box 24)
    - Toxic Tides II: Facility Survey (Folder 744, Box 25)
    - Toxic Tides II: Original - Camera Ready (Folder 745, Box 25)
    - Toxic Tides II: Press Coverage (Folder 746, Box 25)
    - Toxic Tides II: Press Release/Conference (Folder 747, Box 25)
    - Toxic Tides III (Folder 748, Box 25)
    - Toxic Tides Original/Press (Folder 749, Box 25)
    - Toxic Use Reduction - Working Group (Folder 750, Box 25)
    - Toxic Waste Sites NYS Maps (Folder 751, Box 25)
    - Toxic Wastelands (Folder 752, Box 25)
    - Toxics in the Community: National and Local Perspectives (Folder 753, Box 25)
    - Toxics Prevention Act (Folder 754, Box 25)
    - The Toxics-Release Inventory: A National Perspective (Folder 755, Box 25)
    - TOXNET (Folder 756, Box 25)
    - Tracing a River’s Toxic Pollution (Folder 757, Box 25)
    - Turning the Tide: The Case for Toxic Reduction, Aug. 1993 (Folder 758, Box 25)
    - U.S. General Accounting Office Toxic Substance Papers (Folder 759, Box 25)
    - U.S. General Accounting Office Toxic Substance Reports (Folder 760, Box 25)
  - Subseries 1.17: Clean Water Act, 1.17; Box: 26 Folders: 761 - 770
    Series contains The Clean Water Act and correspondence relating to its revision
    - Air Pollution: The Mid-Hudson (Folder 761, Box 26)
    - Clean Water Act 1988 (Folder 762, Box 26)
    - Clean Water Act 1993 (Folder 763, Box 26)
    - Clean Water Act 1993-1994 (Folder 764, Box 26)
    - Clean Water Act 1995 (Folder 765, Box 26)
    - Journal of Air and Waste Management Association (Folder 766, Box 26)
    - New York State Air Guide -1 (Folder 767, Box 26)
    - New York State Air Pollution (Folder 768, Box 26)
    - New York State Air Quality Report Ambient Air Monitoring System (Folder 769, Box 26)
    - United States-Canada Air Quality Agreement (Folder 770, Box 26)
  - Subseries 1.18: St. Lawrence Cement, 1.18; Box: 26 Folders: 771 - 780
    Series contains proposal and plans for the St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project
    - Correspondence (Folder 771, Box 26)
    - Declaration for the Record of Decision (Folder 772, Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 773, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Preliminary Draft, Feb. 29, 2000: Sections 1-7 (Folder 774, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Preliminary Draft, Feb. 29, 2000: Sections 8-R (Folder 775, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Preliminary Draft, Feb. 29, 2000: Appendices (Folder 776, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Draft, Sept. 29, 2000: Sections 1-5 (Folder 777, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Draft, Sept. 29, 2000: Sections 6-R (Folder 778, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Draft, Sept. 29, 2000: Appendices A-B (Folder 779, Box 26)
    - St. Lawrence Cement Greenport Project Draft, Sept. 29, 2000: Appendices C-F (Folder 780, Box 26)
  - Subseries 1.19: Long Island, 1.19; Box: 27 Folders: 781 - 784
    Series contains policy proposals and Resources of Long Island
    - Long Island Sound: An Atlas of Natural Resources (Folder 781, Box 27)
    - Long Island Water Districts (Folder 782, Box 27)
    - Long Island Water Resources Manual (Folder 783, Box 27)
    - Proposed Policies for Long Island Sound Coastal Area (Folder 784, Box 27)
  - Subseries 1.20: NY/NJ Harbor, 1.20; Box: 27 Folders: 785 - 805
    Series contains documents and water quality surveys concerning pollution of the New York/New Jersey Harbor Estuary.
    - A Harbor Like No Other (Folder 785, Box 27)
    - A Report for NY and NJ Residents (Folder 786, Box 27)
    - A Spatial and Seasonal Study of the Benthic Fauna of the Lower Bay of NY Harbor (Folder 787, Box 27)
    - The Future of New York City’s Waterfront (Folder 788, Box 27)
    - Governor’s Island (Folder 789, Box 27)
    - Governor’s Island Clippings (Folder 790, Box 27)
    - Hot Water: A Special Section (Folder 791, Box 27)
    - National Estuary Program: NY/NJ Harbor (Folder 792, Box 27)
    - New York City Waterfront (Folder 793, Box 27)
    - New York City’s Water Supply: Acid Deposition, Inorganic Pollution and the Catskill Reservoirs (Folder 794, Box 27)
    - NY Harbor Water Quality Survey 1986 (Folder 795, Box 27)
    - NY Harbor Water Quality Survey 1987 (Folder 796, Box 27)
    - NY Harbor Water Quality Survey 1991-1992 (Folder 797, Box 27)
    - NY/NJ Harbor Estuary Program Including the NY Bight Restoration Program (Folder 798, Box 27)
    - NY/NJ Harbor Estuary Program Meeting Announcement (Folder 799, Box 27)
    - North River Water Pollution Control Plant (Folder 800, Box 27)
    - Staten Island Freshwater Wetlands Program Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 801, Box 27)
    - The Tidal Exchange (Folder 802, Box 27)
    - Use of Subaqueous Borrow Pits for the Disposal of Dredged Material from the Port of New York-New Jersey Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 803, Box 27)
    - Waste Not, Want Not: Managing New York City’s Water Supply (Folder 804, Box 27)
    - Water for Millions: At What Cost? (Folder 805, Box 27)
  - Subseries 1.21: Nonpoint Pollution, 1.21; Box: 28 Folders: 806 - 830
    Series contains documents concerning Sources and clean-up of nonpoint pollutio
    - Assessment of Erodibility of Sediments in the Thompson Island Pool of the Hudson River (Folder 806, Box 28)
    - Cleaning up New York’s Waters: A Report on New York’s Nonpoint Source Program (Folder 807, Box 28)
    - Coastal Nonpoint Pollution Control Program (Folder 808, Box 28)
    - Conserv 90 (Folder 809, Box 28)
    - Erosion and Sediment Control Guidelines (Folder 810, Box 28)
    - Evaluating the Effectiveness of Proposed Nonpoint Source Control Initiatives (Folder 811, Box 28)
    - Groundwater: A Community Action Guide (Folder 812, Box 28)
    - Groundwater Environmental Protection Agency Handbook (Folder 813, Box 28)
    - Groundwater Protection Manual (Folder 814, Box 28)
    - Groundwater Protection: The Use of Drinking Water Standards by the States (Folder 815, Box 28)
    - Guidance Specifying Management Measures for Sources of Nonpoint Pollution in Coastal Waters (Folder 816, Box 28)
    - Intended Use Plan for the Washington State Water Pollution Control Revolving Fund (Folder 817, Box 28)
    - Non-Industrial Wastewater Pollution can be Managed Better (Folder 818, Box 28)
    - Nonpoint Source Management Program (Folder 819, Box 28)
    - Nonpoint Source Pollution: Runoff of Rain and Snowmelt: Our Biggest Water Quality Problem (Folder 820, Box 28)
    - Nonpoint Source Pollution Strategy and Control (Folder 821, Box 28)
    - Nonpoint Source Reduction Planning Committee for Long Island Sound (Folder 822, Box 28)
    - Nonpoint Source Water Pollution (Folder 823, Box 28)
    - Office of Groundwater and Drinking Water Publications (Folder 824, Box 28)
    - Organic Chemicals and Drinking Water (Folder 825, Box 28)
    - Protecting Groundwater Supplies in River Valley Communities (Folder 826, Box 28)
    - Ramifications of the Safe Drinking Water Act Reauthorization 1986 (Folder 827, Box 28)
    - Reducing the Impacts of Stormwater Runoff from New Development (Folder 828, Box 28)
    - Stormwater Management Guidelines for New Development (Folder 829, Box 28)
    - Upstate New York Groundwater Management Program (Folder 830, Box 28)
  - Subseries 1.22: Estuarine Protection, 1.22; Boxes: 28 - 29 Folders: 831 - 850
    Series contains documents concerning the protection of the Hudson River and its estuaries
    - A Casebook for Successful Urban River Projects (Folder 831, Box 28)
    - An Atlas of the Biological Resources of the Hudson River Estuary (Folder 832, Box 28)
    - Biennial Report Rotating Intensive Basin Studies Water Quality Assessment Program 1987-1988 (Folder 833, Box 28)
    - The Causes and Effects of Acidic Deposition (Folder 834, Box 28)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation Bureau of Water Resources (Folder 835, Box 28)
    - Ebb Tide for Pollution: Actions or cleaning up Coastal Waters (Folder 836, Box 28)
    - Effects of Chlorination of Hudson River Water on the West Branch Reservoir (Folder 837, Box 28)
    - Hudson River Foundation (Folder 838, Box 28)
    - The Hudson, “That River’s Alive” (Folder 839, Box 28)
    - The Lower Hudson River Basin Tributary Study (Folder 840, Box 29)
    - Marine and Estuarine Protection: Programs and Activities (Folder 841, Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Folder 842, Box 29)
    - Model Municipal Harbor Management Plan (Folder 843, Box 29)
    - The Nation’s Water: Key Unanswered Questions about the Quality of Rivers and Streams (Folder 844, Box 29)
    - Papers from the Estuarine Management Practices (Folder 845, Box 29)
    - Principles for Estuarine Impact Assessment (Folder 846, Box 29)
    - Reclassification of Certain Waters in the Hudson River Drainage Basin (Folder 847, Box 29)
    - Saving Bays and Estuaries (Folder 848, Box 29)
    - Strategic Assessment of Near Coastal Waters (Folder 849, Box 29)
    - Stream Health (Folder 850, Box 29)
  - Subseries 1.23: Solid Waste, 1.23; Boxes: 23 - 30 Folders: 851 - 892
    Series contains documents concerning solid waste management and disposal on New York State
    - 6 NYCRR Part 360 Solid Waste Management Facilities (Folder 851, Box 29)
    - A Non-Incineration Solid Waste Management and Recycling Plan (Folder 852, Box 29)
    - A Solid Waste Blueprint for New York State (Folder 853, Box 29)
    - Approaches to Source Reduction (Folder 854, Box 29)
    - Chapter 26 of Division of Waste Management (Folder 855, Box 29)
    - Clippings (Folder 856, Box 29)
    - Comments on Solid Waste Regulation (Folder 857, Box 29)
    - First Report to Congress: Resource Recovery and Source Reduction (Folder 858, Box 29)
    - Fourth Report to Congress: Resource Recovery and Source Reduction (Folder 859, Box 29)
    - Hazardous Waste Reduction: Obstacles and Incentives (Folder 860, Box 29)
    - New Jersey Solid Waste (Folder 861, Box 29)
    - New York State Solid Waste Bills (Folder 862, Box 29)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan (Folder 863, Box 29)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1988-1989 (Folder 864, Box 30)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1989-1990 (Folder 865, Box 30)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1990-1991 (Folder 866, Box 30)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1990-1991 Appendices (Folder 867, Box 30)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1991-1992 (Folder 868, Box 30)
    - New York State Solid Waste Management Plan Responsiveness Summary (Folder 869, Box 30)
    - New York State Waste Reduction Guidance Manual, March 1989 (Folder 870, Box 30)
    - New York State Waste Reduction in the Electronics Industry (Folder 871, Box 30)
    - New York State’s Fourth Annual Hazardous Waste Reduction Conference Proceedings (Folder 872, Box 30)
    - Organized Crime’s Involvement in the Waste Hauling Industry (Folder 873, Box 30)
    - Public Health Assessment: Hertel Landfill (Folder 874, Box 30)
    - Report of the Citizen Task Force on Resource Recovery in New York State (Folder 875, Box 30)
    - Revised 6 NYCRR Part 360 Solid Waste Management Facilities (Folder 876, Box 30)
    - Serious Reduction of Hazardous Waste (Folder 877, Box 30)
    - Solid Waste: A State Responsibility (Folder 878, Box 30)
    - Solid Waste Disposal Capacity in NYS: A Look Ahead to 1997 (Folder 879, Box 30)
    - Solid Waste Management Alternatives: Review of Policy Options to Encourage Waste Reduction (Folder 880, Box 30)
    - Solid Waste Miscellaneous (Folder 881, Box 30)
    - Solid Waste Newsletters (Folder 882, Box 30)
    - Source Reduction (Folder 883, Box 30)
    - Styrofoam Bans (Folder 884, Box 30)
    - Styrofoam Coffee Cup Campaign (Folder 885, Box 30)
    - Summary of Major Developments in Solid Waste Management in New York State, Jan. 1992-Sep.1992 (Folder 886, Box 30)
    - Supplementary Information for a Determination of Completeness: Draft Environmental Impact Statement on Solid Waste Management in Dutchess County, NY (Folder 887, Box 30)
    - Targeting Research Needs for Hazardous Waste Reduction (Folder 888, Box 30)
    - Utica Solid Waste Collection and Disposal (Folder 889, Box 30)
    - Waste Minimization: Major Problems of Data Reliability and Validity Identified (Folder 890, Box 30)
    - Waste Minimization Opportunity Assessment Manual (Folder 891, Box 30)
    - Where Will the Garbage Go? (Folder 892, Box 30)
  - Subseries 1.24: Wastewater Treatment, 1.24; Boxes: 31 - 32 Folders: 893 - 933
    Series contains documents concerning industry waste and treatment of wastewate
    - A Review of Pretreatment Programs in the Great Lakes Basin (Folder 893, Box 31)
    - A Survey and Analysis of Fish Conservation Devices for Water Pumping Facilities having High Volumetric Rates of Intake (Folder 894, Box 31)
    - Alternative Screening Devices at Indian Point, Bowline and Roseton (Folder 895, Box 31)
    - An Empirical Transport Model for Evaluating Entrainment of Aquatic Organisms by Power Plants (Folder 896, Box 31)
    - Besicorp Group Inc. 1995 Annual Report (Folder 897, Box 31)
    - Board on Electric Generation Siting and the Environment (Folder 898, Box 31)
    - Can Business Save the Environment? (Folder 899, Box 31)
    - Chemical Manufacturer’s Association Responsible Care Progress Report (Folder 900, Box 31)
    - Citizen’s Task Force Report on Interim Shutdown of Indian Point (Folder 901, Box 31)
    - Clippings (Folder 902, Box 31)
    - Comments on 1991-1992 Management Plans of the Major Electric Utilities (Folder 903, Box 31)
    - Competitive Opportunities Regarding Electric Services (Folder 904, Box 31)
    - Cooling Towers for Hudson River Power Plants (Folder 905, Box 31)
    - Down the Drain: Toxic Pollution and the Status of Pretreatment in Rhode Island (Folder 906, Box 31)
    - DuPont Chambers Works Waste Minimization Project (Folder 907, Box 31)
    - Dutchess County Water and Wastewater Study (Folder 908, Box 31)
    - Energy/Environmental Issues in the NYS Pulp and Paper Industry (Folder 909, Box 31)
    - Environment Versus the Economy (Folder 910, Box 31)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Pretreatment Manuals (Folder 911, Box 31)
    - General Accounting Office Water Energy Policy Report (Folder 912, Box 31)